Το Plex ζήτησε 120€ για να συνεχίσετε να βλέπετε από τις συσκευές σας.
Το πλήρωσα εγώ το ποσό.
Αν χρησιμοποιείτε συχνά και μπορείτε,
οποιαδήποτε συμβολή θα εκτιμηθεί.
So this fissure was left by your training.
Like a fairy tale
It's a sign the story has reached its end
Like a single passage taken from
A journey that was too long
Of the evil that once cast a shadow
Across this land
And the memories of the short journey
With the hero who defeated it
The story ends
And the hero goes to sleep
Leaving this land with
Days of peace and quiet
The passage of time heartlessly
Makes people forget
Even the tracks left behind by his life
Begin to rust
Just the same
Your words and wishes and courage
Are still inside of me
And they live on
We chose the same path
That's all it was supposed to be
Why is it that at some point
I wanted to understand the reason for
The tears that fall down my cheeks
Even now
If I retrace the journey we walked together
Even though you're not there
I know I'll be able to find it
You don't intend to fight
the dragon, do you?
So why do you continue training?
When I arrived here,
all the villagers wore grim expressions
and lived in fear of the dragon.
Now those same people are smiling happily.
They say this village is safe
because I'm around,
even though I haven't done anything.
The dragon simply hasn't attacked this
village because it doesn't feel like it.
If the dragon attacks the village,
will you fight it?
I don't want to die.
But to the people of this village,
I'm a hero.
I'm Stark, the hero of this village.
I have to defend it.
That said, maybe I'd actually run away.
I got this scar on my forehead during a
fight with my master, not against monsters.
That was the first time he ever hit me.
He must've been disappointed in me.
In the end, he never praised me. Not once.
What?
I don't think you'll run.
You think you know me?
I don't know the first thing about you, but
I recalled my own terrifying experience.
A terrifying experience?
My first battle against a monster.
I'd trained plenty until then.
But my fear made me weak in the knees,
and I ran.
The monster wouldn't stop chasing me.
For some reason, Ms. Frieren
wouldn't help me.
My master was like that, too.
When it finally cornered me
and I steeled my resolve,
my body moved.
All I needed was resolve.
All the training you've done
won't let you down.
Though you're a hopeless coward, I believe
your resolve to protect the village is real.
Resolve, huh?
How did it go?
I don't know.
I don't know,
but I think it'll be all right.
He's not here.
I guess he ran.
It's a shame. I had high hopes for him.
We have no choice.
Fern, we're going to play tag
with the dragon.
What?
Frieren.
You need me to keep it busy
for thirty seconds, right?
You're late.
Will you promise me one thing?
If I die during the battle,
I want you to finish off the dragon.
Very well. I promise.
But why are you willing to go
that far for the villagers?
What?
I just thought it was a strange question.
I've lived in this village for three years.
That's not very long.
Like heck it isn't.
Okay. Let's do this.
Your hands are trembling.
I'm afraid, after all.
You don't have to laugh.
You're just like Eisen.
My master?
Now this is a powerful foe.
Eisen, your hands are shaking.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
You'd admit it, just like that?
Being afraid isn't a bad thing.
It's my fear that brought me this far.
You even tremble the same way.
I see.
My master was afraid, too.
All I need is resolve.
He's entered the dragon's range.
It's not attacking.
It's being cautious.
I thought so.
No wonder it stopped attacking the village.
The dragon is a smart creature.
It's not stupid enough to pick a fight
against a powerful opponent.
Eisen didn't hit Stark for being weak,
or because he was disappointed in him.
We parted in anger.
You hit him?
My body moved on reflex.
I'm sorry for what I did to him.
I was afraid.
I was afraid of him, Frieren.
I couldn't believe it.
My student will become
an incredible warrior.
Now! Fire!
Hey, why aren't you shooting at it?
I did exactly what you told me to do!
You expect me to fight it myself?
You can't be serious, you old hag!
You're just like my master after all!
It's already dead.
What?
An old hag, huh?
I'm scared of what she'll do later.
I... killed it?
I defeated the dragon by myself?
Stark.
You did well.
You exceeded my expectations. Well done.
Look at this mountain of treasure. Yippee!
We can't take it all with us.
No more than three items.
This is ridiculous.
You're interested in this stuff?
This stuff is a mountain of treasure.
My master said that you made the
heroes' adventure ridiculous.
Oh?
He said it was a ridiculous and fun journey.
Wow, you actually made shaved ice!
I told you it was worth searching for.
Not only that, but it's
fluffy instead of icy!
You're right.
This is ridiculous. Should we
be wasting time on this?
Why not? Our journey's only just begun.
The Hero of the South, said to be
humanity's strongest fighter,
was defeated by the Demon King's
Seven Sages of Destruction.
We don't know if we'll make it back alive.
Eisen, would you prefer a
difficult and painful journey?
I'd rather enjoy a ridiculous and fun
journey I can laugh about when it's over.
Look! It melts as soon as you touch it!
Don't touch it. We're going to eat that.
Ridiculous.
By the way, Frieren, what about syrup?
I don't have a spell to produce syrup.
You don't?
Truly ridiculous.
Well? Can you see through them?
Yes, but it's not a very interesting spell.
Sorry my body's not more interesting.
What?
So small.
I'm not small!
So, Stark, what will you do now?
You can go back to Eisen, you know.
My master told you to take me
with you, didn't he?
Besides...
I feel like going on a
ridiculous journey, too.
Monsters are active in the northern lands.
No one's allowed to pass through
the checkpoint currently.
When will the checkpoint open again?
Dunno.
At the very least, we've let none
through since I was posted here,
monsters and people alike.
Excuse me.
Sir, the castellan would like to see you.
I'll be right there.
Listen here, adventurers.
Don't cause any trouble in this town.
That wasn't a very warm welcome.
You're right. He's a good guard.
Harsh on outsiders,
as town guards should be.
Anyway, this city seems safe.
We'll wait here for a while.
It'll be a good opportunity
to take our time studying magic.
Once we drop our things off at the inn,
I'm going to the magic shops.
What? The checkpoint's closed.
It's not like we have a choice.
Go on. You're free to go.
I'm going to get us a room at the inn.
Wanna get something to eat?
Right. I'll go by myself.
Scary...
I heard the sea routes have
been shut down recently, too.
The northern lands' army
plans to defeat them,
but it'll be at least two years
until the checkpoint opens.
Business is at a standstill.
I haven't had this in forever.
The jumbo-berry special.
I was just a kid when I came here before,
so I could hardly finish it.
I had to split it with my master.
I don't remember it being
this small, though.
It seems that way because
you're all grown up now.
I see. I've gotten bigger, huh?
Everything seemed so big when I was a kid.
Even my master's back that
once looked so broad
started looking small at some point.
Eisen's getting up there in age.
I hope you're being a dutiful student.
That's what I'm doing right now.
Really, though, was it always this small?
The passage of time is cruel.
What? Got a problem?
I bought it with my own money.
Excuse me. Could I get a glass of milk?
Sure thing.
What? Why are you mad?
Mr. Stark.
Fine. You can have half.
That's not what I was going to say.
What if I told you we might have to
wait more than two years in this city?
What? No, thanks.
Right? I don't want to, either.
Uh, yeah.
What's her deal?
I'm relieved. You're normal.
Hey, did I do something to offend you?
A way through the checkpoint?
Sure, I'll help you look for one.
Thank you.
Would it be possible to fly over it?
The border with the northern lands
is protected by a powerful barrier that
extends to maximum flying altitude.
It can't be crossed.
That makes sense. Otherwise flying
monsters would get right through.
Then we have no choice.
We'll hit up the merchants' guild.
They might at least be trading.
Trade has been shut down completely.
If guarded caravans aren't allowed through,
then the northern lands
must be quite dangerous.
We'll have to wait until
the situation settles down.
No, let's hit up the black market
and thieves' guild first.
Isn't that a bit dangerous?
We'll be fine. People think I look pretty
strong, and I'm a decent bluffer.
And you've got the face of a scoundrel.
Shut up.
Well, that didn't work.
I shouldn't be surprised. They're
basically fighting a defensive battle.
There's nothing we can do
if the gates won't open.
Well, we've got nothing to lose.
Let's visit the guard station next.
What?
I was just thinking you're being
especially cooperative.
This was your idea.
I thought you didn't want to wait.
You seem more desperate than me.
Well, I don't have a lot of time.
What do you mean?
The view from here is nice, isn't it?
You can see the north side clearly.
When I was little,
my master brought me here.
We departed for the
northern lands from this city.
What was your journey like, Master?
You wanna know? Back then, we...
Normally he hardly spoke about himself,
but he happily told me about
the heroes' adventure.
Across his long life,
nothing was more important to him
than that ten-year adventure.
I'm sure the same is true for Frieren.
I wonder.
But he's too old to travel now.
And he told you to take me with you.
So I need to experience lots of
ridiculous and fun adventures in his place
and bring back stories to tell him.
It's all I can do to repay my debt to him.
If I take too long, my master will die.
Then we can't allow ourselves
to be stopped here.
I bet he's still got plenty
of years left, though.
Ms. Frieren, what are you doing here?
Quiet.
I'm being pursued.
Wh-What did you even do?
I don't know.
I was just visiting various
magic shops, and then...
I'm sorry, Ms. Frieren!
Please forgive me!
Wait. I don't like where this is going.
It seems the guard captain was rude to you.
As the castellan of this city,
I offer my apologies.
It doesn't bother me. He was
just doing his job as a guard.
I'm actually not in any kind of hurry.
I'm taking my time—
You plan to travel north again, don't you?
I hear the northern lands are currently
engaged in an endless conflict
with the remnants of the Demon King's forces.
You must be concerned about
the present situation.
Truly, you have the kindness of a hero.
The people of the northern lands
will be delighted as well.
Please feel free to pass
through the checkpoint.
I can't believe we're getting
through this easily.
Shouldn't we have told them
who you were from the start?
I didn't think there was any point.
I wanted to take my time, anyway.
And I don't really like this kind of thing.
It's an unsettling sight.
I'm glad I got to see it, though.
This must be how my master
departed for the north, too.
You're right.
Aw, darn. I wanted to do
more magical research.
You're still saying that?
We went through a lot of trouble
after that, you know. Right?
Yes.
And you alright
Can you hear me
Trailing along deserted train tracks
Crying excessively
Wanting you to smile
I hold on to memories I'd like to keep fresh
There's something I'd like to tell you
With words more precious than a goodbye
Unremarkable yet special
See, things that couldn't have been
Seen if it weren't for these eyes
Why? They begin to overflow
So, if I were to be born again
I would surely choose this place once more
So, if we were to meet again
I'd never let you go, I'd choose the present
Even if no promises were made
Even if I'm lost in days of loneliness
Those tears will be alright,
dawn will surely break
I'm whispering our lullaby
for you to come back home
It hurts...
Humans love to make a fuss.
He died in battle against
Aura ten years ago.
Mom...
The Liberation Festival is tonight.
Then we'd be no different from the demons.
They're capable of speech.
I'm curious about that mage.
What a pain in the rear...
It's like a fairy tale.